[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "I don’t mind __ with the cooking but I am not going to was the dishes.",
    "options": ["for helping", "to held", "helping", "help"],
    "answer": "helping"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "I decided to go __ with my friend as I needed some exercise.",
    "options": ["to a walk", "for a walk", "for a walking", "walk"],
    "answer": "for a walk"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "My uncle arrived while I __ the dinner.",
    "options": ["was cooking", "had cooked", "would cook", "cook"],
    "answer": "was cooking"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "In order to improve farming methods, we need __.",
    "options": ["machine", "machinery", "a machinery", "machineries"],
    "answer": "machinery"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "My friend always goes home __ foot.",
    "options": ["with", "on a", "on", "by"],
    "answer": "on"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "We need two hundred dollars __ this to pay for everything.",
    "options": ["as well", "also", "beside", "besides"],
    "answer": "besides"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "The team is __ eleven players.",
    "options": ["made up of", "made of", "made up", "made"],
    "answer": "made up of"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "My wife reminded me __.",
    "options": [
      "to my appointment",
      "to go my appointment",
      "of my appointment",
      "my appointment"
    ],
    "answer": "of my appointment"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "At least one of the students __ full marks every time.",
    "options": ["get", "gets", "are getting", "have got"],
    "answer": "gets"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Please __ the necessity of arriving early.",
    "options": ["emphasise on", "emphasise to", "emphasise about", "emphasise"],
    "answer": "emphasise on"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "I don’t think you will have any difficulty __ a driving license.",
    "options": ["to get", "in getting", "for getting", "get"],
    "answer": "to get"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "I thought that __ was the last one.",
    "options": [
      "prettiest one of all",
      "the prettiest one from all",
      "the prettiest one of all",
      "the most prettiest of all"
    ],
    "answer": "the prettiest one of all"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "The ministers arrived __ a decision last night.",
    "options": ["by", "to", "on", "at"],
    "answer": "at"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "She is beautiful but she is ___ her mother.",
    "options": [
      "most beautiful",
      "less beautiful",
      "as beautiful",
      "not so beautiful as"
    ],
    "answer": "not so beautiful as"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "The government gave __ the demands of the people.",
    "options": ["into", "in", "to", "over to"],
    "answer": "in"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "The second World War broke __ in september, 1939.",
    "options": ["through", "away", "out", "in"],
    "answer": "out"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "Choose the correct meaning of the following words: Gullible",
    "options": [
      "easily deceived",
      "simple",
      "foolish",
      "willing to believe anything or anyone"
    ],
    "answer": "willing to believe anything or anyone"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Choose the correct meaning of the following words: Viable",
    "options": ["that will work", "capable", "that can be done", "possible"],
    "answer": "that will work"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Choose the correct meaning of the following words: Handy",
    "options": [
      "comfortable",
      "useful",
      "convenient to handle or use",
      "necessary"
    ],
    "answer": "useful"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Select the pair that best expresses a relationship similar to that expressed in the original pair: Conscious- Careless",
    "options": [
      "Well-informed- Knowing little",
      "Graceful- Ugly",
      "Generous- Unkind",
      "Careful- Indifferent"
    ],
    "answer": "Careful- Indifferent"
  }
]
